I'll let you I won't take I won't see
your moment I won't see your
moment like this is like the most of
course this is Joel mement that I can
possibly think of is like there's some
super awesome you know Niche piece of
technology that I'm ready to blow your
mind about and you're like oh yeah I use
that for my terminal or like the most
like a random thing exactly
[Music]
hey guys real quick I just wanted to
tell you about our sponsor threat Locker
now wait wait before you hit this SK
forward button let me just say this most
of the stuff that holds my attention
nowadays is red team stuff as well but I
sat down with the threat Locker team
this past week to do a demo of their EDR
software and it was super technically
fascinating how this thing works so
check this out you drop this thing on a
system right and for the first week or
so it's creating a policy and a profile
for that system it's logging all the
executables uh what child processes are
being spawned uh the files and their
hashes that sort of thing and it's
creating this policy okay then after the
learning mode is up we're in secured
mode and that policy gets put into place
and anything that's not on that allow
list is immediately autod denied that's
the zero trust piece right so in
addition to that they've got a bunch of
crazy features like ring fencing and
dynamic access controls that would stop
a malicious hacker at pretty much every
step along the way actually I I was
watching this demo and I was kind of
freaked out because I have no idea how I
would cope with getting dropped into a
threat locker system as a red teamer
anyway if you want to learn more about
this head over to threat locker.com and
request a demo and when you do ask for
my boy Andrew his demo was super to the
point and he was able to answer all my
technical questions all right cool back
to the
show all right dude we're ring so I have
literally been that what is that Charlie
conspiracy theory dude this week just
like pointing you got the string on the
on the bolted board that is that has
been me this week with CSS injection man
um there has been some really cool stuff
popping up in CSS injection and
actually there's been some cool stuff
that is like seven years old at this
point that I'm just now finding out
about um that is absolutely amazing so
I'm excited to cover that today but
first let's get to the news the news
Joel with the news
report so space
raccoon space do you want to start with
that one or should we start with yeah
yeah so space Aron has a really cool um
blog post that he came out with um
talking about um well universal code
execution I don't should we talk about
the the wording of that so so I think
it's interesting I think it's
interesting cuz when I went into this I
was like um okay you know that sounds
real real intense yeah and and as you
start reading through it um first of all
let me just say it's extraordinarily
well done research um as always as
always classic space raccoon stuff um
however there are a lot of conditions
for this for this actual exploit to be
met and essentially what this this
article outlines is like
some of the functionality surrounding
Chrome extensions and how um the
developer
documentation and some of the ways that
you have to communicate with these
extensions can be um manipulated to
result in code execution on the client
um on on the actual client running the
Chrome extension in their browser um and
and I think I learned a lot about Chrome
extension architecture from this one and
I think the way that he deals with
essentially the massive amount of
conditions required for this attack is
pretty awesome uh essentially using
large data sets to query um Chrome
extensions that uh fit a c certain
profile but man there are a lot of
conditions yeah for sure and I think
it's like it's a great example of one of
those sort of Niche areas of research
where once you start to dig into how
these things work you find a lot of
really interesting topic specific
information about you know pit Falls or
weird configurations or just like
strange behavior and stuff like that um
and I think this is really really useful
as a whole I haven't seen a whole lot of
research done about Chrome extensions
and I know that there's a lot of
programs that own or have a Chrome
extension that's in scope usually um and
I think a lot of people don't really
test it because it's it's not very easy
to test it's kind of falls into that
weird gray area of both like web hacking
but also code analysis type stuff um so
there's definitely it's very interesting
and it's definitely Fringe Fringe web
hacking you know it's like there's
JavaScript you know obviously heavily
involved in there but it's using a bunch
of like Chrome apis that's hooking it's
like a combination of desktop hacking
and and uh and web hacking which I think
is a really cool area and I don't know
if you've seen the content calendar yet
Joel but I added some stuff on there and
we do have an episode coming up soon on
Chrome extension hacking which is going
to be super awesome so I think this is a
nice little little intro into this do
you want to do the um the the tldr for
this one or or should I yeah you you go
ahead because um yeah I I I did look
into it pretty pretty well and
essentially what he does here is he
explains uh Chrome extension
architecture uh and essentially there's
this whole concept of a a Content script
which is essentially a script that gets
added to each individual page or that is
within the scope for that uh Chrome
extension um so that you can run
JavaScript uh and and that that JS code
has access to the Dom but doesn't have
access to like JavaScript variables and
stuff like that on the page um and so
it's sort of living in its own little
isolated world I think that's actually
the technical term uh uh which is cool
um and and because of that you know
there are some some limitations on on
what it can do and essentially one of
the most common ways for uh people to
structure these these uh
content uh what are they called again
content scripts there we go I was like
wait a second what is going on here um
the these content strips is to be able
to communicate with the front end via
post message okay so you're sending a
post message to from this content script
up to uh the browser extension uh sort
of backend the the uh post message
listener that's kind of sitting on the
back end and then you're passing through
that data to other uh sort of Chrome
extension
apis like for example the um the I can't
get the name of it right here it's the
native um send send message the one that
allows you to actually send a message to
a native application on the front end
there's so many like terms and stuff
that we're just not like used to again
this is like one of those weird you know
it's such a niche area that has so many
um quirks just to that are specific to
it yeah yeah and and so there's this I
finally found the section of of the of
the app here it's it's send native
message and essentially what that allows
you to do from the the Chrome uh
extension backend is interface directly
with a native application on the local
device so this is for stuff like um
using password managers and and that
sort of thing um and essentially it just
does this via standard in andout and the
whole premise of his research is like
okay um if there's a way for us to
interact with these content scripts and
then that content script passes the
message straight through through to the
back end and then passes the message
straight through to the the native
message Api right now we're passing uh
this this data directly through to a
native application on the back end and
then that native application handles um
the user input in in a bad way then uh
then vulnerabilities can happen so it's
like there's like a a set of like one
two three four conditions uh that must
happen for this like attack chain to
work and then he's like so it gets
pretty complex but here is this massive
data set called the Chrome extension
manifest data set that you can use to
query and then here's the semrep role
and it just shows how he takes you know
the set of conditions program you know
writes a program to detect these and
then sprays it across the whole data set
and actually ends up finding um a a
vulnerability in a plugin with like what
was it like two million I think there's
two million installs on it yeah uh uh he
I don't think he mentioned what the
actual one was but he said it had 2
million users yeah yeah one such
extension is the extension extension B
quote unquote with two million installs
um which is awesome so it's really cool
to see him sort of have an idea on how
this research should work and
then programiz it and then find things
that are actually vulnerable to it
across the whole uh extension data set
um and then pop some cool bugs with it
very very yeah yeah absolutely I mean
it's really like that start to finish of
finding a bug figuring out how to do it
end mass and then like doing it like at
scale and then reporting all that stuff
and you know it's it's really awesome to
you know see a great example of that
especially in a niche research like this
yeah okay so to try to be a little bit
more concise and clear with my
explanation here okay the content script
has a has a post message listener it
takes data from that post message
listener sends it to the Chrome backend
via send message and then there's an
insecure handling of send message it
passes it through to send native message
which is now hitting a native app on the
uh on the actual device and then the
native app incorrectly handles that data
and introduces a a vulnerability in the
system the example that he has is like a
path traversal um to to load us a dll
and essentially he forced the download
of a dll because he's got control of JS
right in the browser you can force the
download
and then uh loads that that URL or that
dll um From the Path traversal on the
back end and gets RC so um pretty crazy
chain definitely worth a read because it
helps me understand a little bit better
how Chrome extensions work and what kind
of functionality they have surrounding
them and I think let me just add this
one more thing I think the fact that he
talks about common patterns in Chrome
extensions is like that sort of stuff is
really helpful to know because
in order to get that intuition of like
what's a common pattern what's not a
common pattern you have to read through
a lot of Chrome extension code bases
which is going to take a lot of time and
Eugene saved us that time with this
write up yeah it's that sort of like
meta knowledge stuff like how what's all
the ways to open or to reference a
window in a browser like that kind of
research is um that's really valuable
even when it's I mean as a whole that's
not really what the purpose of this blog
is but it's kind of just nested in there
as a little tree which is awesome yeah a
little bonus a little bonus um all right
so actually kind of a thin week as far
as news goes um the only one that I had
otherwise here besides obviously all of
the CSS injection stuff that I'm going
to freak out about uh later later on in
this episode literally I'm sleep
deprived right now because I've just
been so I was laying in bed last night
and I was trying to fall asleep and I
was just like my brain just kept on
churning CSS injection stuff um what is
wrong with you dude I don't know it's
not not even that crazy of a v either
it's like it's like very Fringe this is
like literally like like awake at night
like restless thinking about CSS like
I've got problems man I've got problems
okay so before but before we get to that
let's cover this next one okay so um
this one was just kind of uh this is a
tweet from um
Isa Adia sorry I don't know how to
pronounce it and I'm I automatically put
like a Japanese spin on it for some
reason if it's fits to to Japanese
characters um but essentially what this
person tweeted out was uh a way to
escalate client side path universals
essentially in script tags
using the uh built-in Json P callback
that's a part of Wordpress websites
which we've talked about probably two or
three times at this point um on the
podcast so nothing super new there but
it did get my brain turning a little bit
and I wanted to shoot out a prediction
really quickly and and ask for the
community to do some research or at
least keep their eyes peeled uh for a
variant of this which is essentially if
we can find something in like WordPress
or Drupal or like some of these big fra
or like um for example Cloud flare CDN
CGI right if we could find something
right you know on these very widely used
Frameworks uh that allows us to
arbitrarily control the
response the Json formatted
response that would be extremely helpful
for exploiting client side patch versals
okay so essentially here you know they
have a Json P call back you're able to
specify you know what JavaScript
function is used to trigger the call
back that's great we've talked about it
a million times what I want is an
endpoint where I can specify arbitrary
Json in the query parameter and it
returns that that Json in the response
should
it just just reflects it right down into
the response and the reason why that's
extremely helpful is that if you have a
client side path driver Soul obviously
um you're controlling where that API
request is being sent to um and you but
it is expecting the same some data
format back because it thinks it's
communicating with the same API endpoint
that it's always you know always
communicated with so what you what
essentially needs to happen is we need
to find a way for to give it the data
format that it expects in Json as as a
response and then we can use that to
trigger
xss you know business logic bugs uh open
redirects like these are all cases that
I've seen um when you're able to
actually control that arbitrary Json
response and normally my my go-to way to
do this Joel is i i i redirect off the
domain to my domain right and then I
control the Json response but that
requires an open redirect and if we can
find a gadget in like WordPress or
something like that that allows us to do
this then uh we wouldn't have to
redirect off domain we would we would
just be able to do it with like a
semi-open redirect um or even a closed
redirect the domain or even some sort of
browser specific feature like I know
there's some really interesting research
recently that I've seen about blobs like
BL like uh like those like ephemeral
sort of uh file blob things that are in
the browser um and you can like
reference them and technically the or is
actually wherever they came from so like
if you have a blob that was created on
example.com and you're referencing like
you have an xss in that blob for example
the origin or like you know domain um
like window. domain um or
document.domain is going to be the host
that the blob was created on oh really
so I I don't know if it has access to
cookies and all that kind of stuff I
think there's some like weird
limitations around that but yeah
potentially also something like that
where you have some sort of brows
specific feature that would allow you
control the file contents would be
Factory that would be really cool blobs
I think have a a custom scheme that's
associated with yes it's like blon HP
yeah so so I I'm wondering whether in
the scenarios in these client side path
traversal like scenarios whether we
could hit those maybe if there was like
a redirect that was doing some domain
level validation but wasn't checking the
scheme or something like that then you
could definitely have something like
that happen but I like I like the way
you're thinking
thinking outside the box some critical
thinking thinking like a hacker aren't
you think I'm thinking like a hacker hey
where did I get this shirt critical
critical critical I I love how I'm like
uh obsessing over client side pth or um
CSS injection and CLI side patal lately
and this is you know these almost are
never critical critical criticals you
know yeah almost never we got we got to
start talking about critical critical
critical um well actually I guess on
that note on that note uh I will take a
tangent on something that is not here in
the doc Joel which is that um I'm giving
a talk at defcom this year that I was
also frantically preparing last night
for the deadline that was last night um
uh
surrounding like some of the coolest
critical reports that I've found over
the past couple years of bug Bounty so
there's 11 bugs in there all of them are
criticals um critical critical criticals
and uh and so if you're interested in
hearing a bunch of bug stories uh about
about those definitely check out uh bug
Bounty Village talk that I'll be doing
at Defcon I think it's entitled I don't
even know the title off the top of my
head I think it's like top wor stories
from a tryhard bugy hunter or something
like that so be on the lookout for that
self self-promotion Shameless
self-promotion there did you have to
complete your slides like fully yeah
dude did w which is like a pain because
it's like a month in advance it makes
sense because they've got a lot of stuff
to recover or to uh to cover and and you
know assess but um man it it was a lot
yeah it was like slides I mean
especially this far in advance that's a
that's a ton yeah I think we can make
small modifications to it between now
and then but essentially they said it
needs to be like as finalized as
possible like okay well that's pretty no
procrastinating allowed yeah apparently
not damn cool all right let's uh you
want to talk about your your special
critical thinkers release and then we'll
we'll Okay cool so yesterday very
exciting yesterday I dropped passion
project of mine that uh I've been
working on for the past couple weeks
that I just kind of bulldozed my whole
schedule and worked on this because I
had the motivation and that is
essentially a full-time bug Bounty
blueprint how to go full time on bug
Bounty it's like a 15-page document
describing essentially if I were having
a personal conversation with you and you
were saying I want to go full-time B
Bounty what should I do this is what I
would say to you at length um so it's
very conversationally written it covers
a lot of topics sort of ranging
from um what kind of difficulties you're
going to face as a full-time book Bounty
Hunter what kind of um like personality
traits uh or um I guess like motivation
uh deficits you might uh come up against
that that are going to going to cause
problems um we cover taxes we cover um
like all the good stuff yeah like how
how to how to collaborate with other
hackers how to quit your job and and
transition into full-time Buck Bounty
how to make sure you your finances are
squared in advance um and then
essentially how to build a pipeline
surrounding you know your bug Bounty
skills and keep on driving that stuff in
to create a good consistent income
stream for you that you can live off of
so um it's it's not to shoot my own horn
here it's pretty good I think it's
really good and and the feedback has
been positive so um definitely check
that out if you're interested critical
thinkers um if you're not a critical
thinker head over to Discord check out
the server subscriptions that we've got
there um this book is only available to
the critical thinkers um so even if you
want you know go ahead drop a sub it's
25 bucks for one month grab the book and
bounce that's fine too but uh in that
one month I think you'll find critical
thinkers to is something special man
there's a lot of great conversations
happening in that in that uh in that
sort of exclusive Discord Channel and a
lot of cool um a lot of cool scripts a
lot of cool techniques good
conversations happening in there so
check it out if you haven't already yeah
absolutely exclusive masterg glasses and
stuff too all all we do masterg glasses
at least once a month um or hack alongs
too um and we record all of them we put
them all in in there so historic you you
know you have months of back content
that you get out access to and so lots
of really cool features if you want to
go check it out yeah absolutely um oh
yeah one other cool feature that is
actually um in the the critical thinkers
exclusive content Channel that I wanted
to just kind of shout out um is the
client side path traversal browser
extension that uh me and and bus Factor
wrote um bus factor is a a very valued
member of the critical thinking uh
community and we were just kind of
discussing what it would look like to
build a browser extension for client
side path rers
and I like threw some kind of junk Cod
at him I was like this is kind of
roughly how it would work and I come
back the next day and he's like
converted it all to typescript and like
has a build flow and like all these nice
little buttons and stuff like that and
I'm like oh man this this rocks so I
kind of took it from there as well and
and did some additional modifications
for it but at this point it's pretty
good it detects pretty consistently um
when you have data reflected from uh you
know the query parameters the hash a
couple other areas into the of a sub
resource you know request whether it be
like an if frame or a fetch or something
like that um those are things that we
all want to know about um so we have
that extension available um to the
critical thinkers as well and I think
probably at some point we'll we'll
release it probably within the next year
or so but I definitely want to refine it
a little bit and uh get it to a spot
where you know some of the the
difficulties are ironed out some of the
false positives are ironed out um before
we release it fulltime yeah definitely
def have a couple really good plug-in
ideas in the in the pipeline I think I
know we've talked about a variety of
different things um some of them we may
have even cut out of the episode
recording so um yeah we'll we'll
definitely be creating those and
releasing those eventually uh to the
community as we go just for our own
purposes and also just to share the
share the knowledge with the critical
thinkers but yeah yeah no
absolutely hey guys real quick I just
wanted to give a shout to the hacker
content team they have been absolutely
killing it the past couple months taking
the content from the podcast and
condensing it down into consumable
social media posts whether it be shorts
or text posts or whatever they've been
rocking it so uh I just wanted to give
them a shout out and let you know that
they do all sorts of cyber security
content as well as social media
management they do technical blogs they
do uh comprehensive social media
management uh so if your organization
could benefit from any of those types of
services make sure you head over to
hacker content.com drop them a line and
mention the podcast when you do to get
your first month of cyber security
content marketing services for free all
right that's it let's get back to the
pot all right man the moment has come
CSS injection time your your moment my
moment unfold the The Conspiracy Theory
all right man here's here's what I got
okay so I didn't know until last week
that CSS injection has been pretty much
completely solved prior to this I
thought that essentially we had a really
reliable way to leak the contents of
like attributes and that sort of thing
but um actually it is possible to leak
the content of a text node as well right
just the inner HTML or whatever of a
specific element if that's text um does
it require user interaction so I mean of
course the user has to navigate to the
thing but once they navigate as long as
you can do an import um from a a remote
uh CSS page I guess then you're good to
go um and and you can block that with
CSP right yes you can so if if we're
talking about remed
methods CSP is pretty much the the best
way to do this uh obviously besides like
not introducing the vulnerability in the
first place which I think is not too
hard to do with CSS injection like you
need a pretty Niche scenario um for CSS
injection to happen in the first place
but I guess I mean it should follow most
of the same like instances of any other
type of xss or HTML injection right
where you're just some sort of content
is making its way unsanitized into the
the response body so in the same way
that you would sanitize any of the rest
of those you'd probably fix that as well
right yeah exactly but we don't need to
dwell on how to fix it Joel We need to
dwell on how to explain it okay just
some of us do take your take your
program manager [__] away from me okay
like we don't need that right now this
is this is my moment um okay so there
there are two things that I kind of want
to talk about today and give the
listeners a tldr on
essentially what CSP injection has to
offer and like how to actually expl okay
so first one is of course the one that I
think most people are familiar with this
is the one that I was using um to
exploit CSP injection uh up until this
point which is essentially the research
done by uh donut doing using sequential
um import chaining and was just back
from like Singapore right some was that
the was it that event I don't know when
he originally came out vas or something
I remember it was a long it was a while
ago pre Co no yeah it absolutely was and
and uh it's been I mean it's been out
for a long time at this point but
essentially this is the whole concept of
like you have a CSS import statement
right you've got that like at import
feature with with CSS and you import a
remote stylesheet and that stylesheet
REM includes another remote stylesheet
and does some CSS rule that will trigger
a call back right and what what will
happen is you don't on the server side
you don't respond to that second
stylesheet import until you've gotten
the call back from the first uh set of
rules that you put in there to leak the
first character whatever right once
you've done that once you've got that
first character leaked then you respond
and you do the same thing recursively
until you have leaked the whole content
of like a uh an HDML attribute and the
whole point the whole reason why this is
possible is because you can use the the
starts with um selector for for CSS
stuff so essentially you're doing a
carrot equal sign and then you know
whatever value and and you're able to
specify okay uh if the attribute starts
with this then you know trigger this
HTTP request via like background image
or whatever um and it since you're able
to do that you can just by character by
character by character by character just
Brute Force out um the value of these
attributes which is which is super cool
um and has been
absolutely uh very very relevant and
very much used in in the in the uh
Community for CSS injection and was what
I was using up until this point to prove
most of my impact um this this was and
just to be clear this was um released by
donut and uh another guy Pepe V at the
exact same same time around 2019 range
um and so that is a wellestablished
technique you knew all that right Joel
oh yeah yeah of course all that yeah
because I know how much you love CSS
injection and all these little Fringe
web web vulner you on the darket they
call me the CSS injection
Master thanks for that thanks for that
man okay so um cool so I went in the
rabbit hole this week because of some
other things that I'll mention later but
while I was in that rabbit hole um I I
found a little bit more research on this
specific technique that I didn't know
about before so I wanted to share it
with the community which is um this
technique it's pretty fast
uh I think it only takes like a couple
seconds to to maybe 10 seconds or so to
leak a decent Siz token but um you can
double the speed of it by also
simultaneously selecting from the
backside of of the the the um attribute
the HTML attribute that you're trying
suddenly became a computer science leak
code problem right so so it's like you
know you're Bri forcing the characters
you're coming in you're coming in and
eventually you're converging somewhere
right um and I thought that was really
interesting it doubles the speed and it
makes total sense why that would why
that would work um so cool little little
addition there um that's awesome the the
other thing that I wanted to kind of
shout out in this same like leaking
attributes section is this uh repo by um
Port swiger research called CSS
exfiltration which I think was a repo
that was related to like some write up
they did back in 2020 I believe um and
this was like recent Gareth Hayes
research right so this was not recent or
the blog or the exfiltration thing was I
mean so recently um Gareth Hayes came
out with a a blog post on blind uh CSS
exfiltration and this was one of the
things that like kind of triggered me uh
a while back back into CSS injection um
very cool project I think we've talked
about it once or twice before in the pot
if not just Google Blind CSS
exfiltration it's literally the only
article on it out there cuz what talk
about a friend FR uh piece of security
research like that is the epitome of
Fringe um but this is actually something
different Joel this is some research
that he had done years before and it's
really it's really interesting because
this repo contains like one two 3 four
five six like over 10 different
techniques for leaking um characters
from different contexts uh via CSS
injection so he's got like steel end
characters in Firefox steel reverse
Firefox steel script contents like all
of these various I like I'm on Shaz
seriously man it's like he's got a bunch
of really cool ways of doing this and
one of the ones that kind of stood out
to me and I was like oh man I didn't
know that was possible was that um you
can steal the contents of an attribute
by using the attr function in CSS okay
check this out Joel I'm gonna I'm going
to link it to you and because I don't
think I put it like super clearly in the
doc I'm you are in CSS yeah so click
that link that I just sent you in
Discord Okay so so on line on line five
we'll drop this in the description um uh
on line five there is a essentially a um
a Content CSS attribute that is defined
uh defining a property in CSS and the
value of that content so the content is
of course used to add like a prefix or a
postfix to a specific div or whatever
the content of that is
at function call and then the name of
the attribute and essentially what that
will do is set the in this scenario the
after content so the content that comes
after this div uh to be this value of a
specific attribute right and then you
can you can style that after attribute
with a specific font that will
exfiltrate all the data from that so
this whole like
HTTR um function in CSS I think is
really fascinating that you can access
HTML attributes and stick their content
into the the content property in CSS
pretty yeah I'm curious I'm curious how
far that extends cuz I know that there
are certain like weird things like
doesn't dot value like
implicitly um contain like whatever
you've put into like a for like a form
input for example right so like would
the value attribute from CSS on a form
input contain that value or would it be
would it have to be explicitly said I
don't know you know it's funny you
mention dot value cuz do value is a
little weird right I feel like there are
some Frameworks that will like
automatically update the dot value
or like essentially the value HTML
attribute and I know that if you use
like in JavaScript if you use value that
it it just dumps the content of a like
an input field or something like that
but I think sometimes it doesn't update
it um for things like HTML and CSS it
just does it in the JavaScript context
so that's an interesting question I'm
not I'm not sure the answer to that one
yeah yeah but I'd be curious to see if
there's other you know weird cases like
that or any implicit attributes or
anything like that like that's exists
but isn't you know visible all the time
stuff like that you're starting to feel
it right Joel like this is interesting
[__] right it it's super weird I I mean
it makes you wonder like why does
something like that exist I don't I
don't know I'm sure there's some use
case and there's probably some other
weird Edge case stuff that exists just
like it well CSS injection or css in
general is just getting stronger and
stronger and stronger right as they
introduce new new features so that's one
of the things that I like really keep an
eye out for in in the browser um change
logs is like what features are they
adding to CSS and how does that affect
our current understanding of CSS and I
was a lot more motivated to do this when
I thought that text node content so
essentially if you have something in
like let's say inside an H1 tag you want
to leak like you know High Joel or
something like that you want to leak the
person's name um I thought that that was
not solved but that actually is solved
which is crazy to me um so now I'm a
little bit less motivated to be honest
this has been a little bit demotivating
this whole research uh thing that I've
been on like oh well they figured it all
out um but now you know yes yes now I
know um and and so okay before before we
get too far down that down that path I'm
going to go ahead and paste this uh this
link link that I was talking
about in the dock see you know many
other podcasts other YouTubers even they
forget to put the links in the
description you have always that
critical thinking not us we don't forget
we don't forget unless a master class
that I wrote Iran and then it takes me a
week of forgetting Joel what are you
doing oh man all right so CSS selectors
to leak the contents of HTML attributes
boom done of course that's that's done
that's been done for a while but the
problem is nowadays we have uh single
page applications that are pretty much
everywhere right um and they don't often
have input Fields with pre-populated
values like Cerf token or like API token
or something like that often times that
gets stuck inside of a script text node
right uh and just populated directly
into JavaScript as a part of like those
I don't know what do they call it's like
like seed data almost for the page it's
like a Json blob yeah like the state or
whatever yeah like state that yeah
exactly the the state like Json blob
right that's where all the juicy stuff
is nowadays um and that's why this
research is so crazy which by the way is
so awesome when you find like a single
xss because then you just have one giant
Json that's included on every page has
us token and all the config parameters
it's so nice window yeah exactly exactly
love that and we can now we can do that
also with um with CSS injection okay and
the way we do this is via this crazy
absolutely nuts technique that I'm just
I love I always know when Justin puts a
tweet in the doc that is just written
entirely in Japanese and is is like
three days old it's going to be some
crazy crazy research that he's about to
so masat kinugawa does some amazing
amazing research man uh and So lately
what he's been up to which triggered
this whole thing was he tweeted out in
Japanese about um some of the uh
research he's been doing on font
ligatures and how he's been applying
that to Lava Moe which is a an
absolutely or lava dome in particular
lava mode I think is the company above
it so so check out this this product
Joel it's like a little bit further down
in the dock but like essentially this
product lavadome is a a Dom element
isolator so essentially you can have a a
piece of the Dom that you just cannot
get the value from from JavaScript you
can have xss and you just won't be able
to like get the value out of this uh
this piece of the Dom um why not well
they isolate it out they do a bunch of
um just crazy stuff to
JavaScript yeah yeah so like you
literally can't get it and there's a
bunch of conditions to it right so if
you if you go to the lava JavaScript uh
we believe this is a solvable problem is
yeah pretty crazy right that they they
could they think they can actually
isolate a node from the rest of the Dom
and you just can't touch it and they
call it like you know Shadow Dom is a
feature for metam Master's show Private
key toggle which exposes the private key
on in plain text currently the Sens of
content is attached to the Dom once is
exported making it fully accessible to
all NC's running right so they're saying
this the whole concept of this project
is is um quote we live in a world where
we can no longer trust the code in our
own apps and same origin execution does
not guarantee safety and I'm like okay
all right let's go and and um it's
amazing because they're essentially
trying to protect the value of some you
know HTML inext from themselves which is
like a very difficult problem to solve
and I can just
like the moment that masato kinugawa
started looking at this project like it
it's over man because there's a bunch of
like issues in this project that he has
submitted like leaking the values of of
uh you know lavadome via character
height in font ligatures in mouseover in
text fragments and like there's just a
bunch of crazy ways that he's done it um
but overall I mean very interesting
project and I think most of the time the
approach like they mention in their in
their read me is to actually put that
sensitive content in an isolated eye
frame um but apparently they say you
know you could put it in isolated eye
frame but that doesn't feel as cool or
something like that and why don't you
put it in lava dome
instead which is like
okay yeah okay and
then and then Masa kigawa is like no no
no I will not allow for this um so
essentially he's tweeting out about all
of these different ways to steal it and
and one of the ones that he he tweeted
out was very much related to uh CSS
injection which is essentially like you
can use um font
ligatures uh to to leak the content of
this of this uh you know sort of
encapsulated Dom okay yeah do you know
what a font ligature is Joel I do know
what a font ligature is why do you know
what a font ligature is because I use
Font ligatures what yeah so okay so of
course you do of course you know about
this the tldr here is that my my the the
terminal setup that I use it uses a font
that uses ligatures specifically in both
VSS code and it term to convert like
double equals into a fancy thing or
triple equals into a fancy character or
equals right arrow to a fancy arrow and
that kind of stuff so do you know here
what I'll let you I won't take I won't
see your moment I won't see your moment
what like this is like the most of
course this is Joel mement that I can
possibly think of is like there's some
super awesome you know Niche piece of
technology that I'm ready to blow your
mind about and you're like oh yeah I use
that for my terminal or like the most
like a random thing exactly like just
like absolute Tech Enthusiast [__] you
could Poss think of um that's hilarious
dude okay so font ligatures essentially
what this what this allows you to do is
when you have a custom font you can
specify a sequence of characters that
has a a custom glyph so glyph being the
the sort of actual um visual
representation of the character yeah so
essentially what you can do um is you
can Define any length of of uh font
ligature so you can have a font ligature
that's like 30 characters long or or
more right where if it sees this 35
character sequence it displays it with a
separate GIF GI does not display a gif
glyph thank you all of a sudden you
start typing and then all like the the
conspiracy Charlie pops up or whatever
oh
man it's so good um so anyway you can
Define these these uh special um
ligatures and this allows you to
actually leak the content of uh a text
node so very similar to what we're
you're doing with the CSS selectors
essentially you
can have it you can load up a custom
font on into this specific text node and
then um that font has these ligatures
and if um everything else every other
character A through Z you know 0o
through nine that sort of thing is set
to a zero width character you can
control the width of of the the
characters in the font um the custom
font creation process but the ligature
that you're trying to leak is massive
you know it's like 10,000 pixels or
something like that wide okay and then
you style the container that this text
is in such that if um if it's above a
certain length there is a uh or above a
certain width there is a scroll bar that
appears right so that can give you a
binary yes or no on whether this uh
ligature is actually created or not
right um because when the scroll bar
appears you can style the scroll bar to
have a background image that will reach
back out to your server
right okay did you see what you see what
I'm doing here the shadow yeah Shadow d
by the way that's a whole Rabbit Hole
too I I'd never heard of that and it's
just like yeah is that what you've been
doing for the past couple minutes while
I've been explaining this Joel I wasn't
I was in the beginning but I am paying
attention I'm all right I I could see
the the classic moment when Joel says
Shadow Dom that sounds either
that sounds interesting in so many
ways um so anyway font liur super cool
essentially um what you have to do to to
make this whole this whole process work
is you've got to set up a uh recursive
um CSS import like we were talking about
in the beginning um Alla donut and pepe
v um
and what it it just sounds like a meme I
don't like Pepe V like I mean am I
saying the name right like twitch
emotes it does sort of like oh [__] cuz
it's like I am saying the the name right
right oh geez that's gonna be sorry Mr V
if I am not saying it it right no I
mean yeah I mean that's the name so wow
you just made fun of this guy's name and
his in his amazing research on on CSS in
it's a cool name I'm just it is it was
the Cadence I don't know maybe maybe it
was the Cadence okay so anyway you use
the recursive import I'm just going to
call it Donuts research via Donuts
research there right
and like I'm not gonna risk Tri your G
again his name his name has been erased
because of your your Tendencies Joel um
uh and so you're essentially recursively
importing these these stylesheets you're
waiting for the call back before you
respond to the next one and essentially
each time you're forcing the style sheet
to load up a new font which you are
dynamically generating to have ligatures
which are expanding with each character
that has been leaked um and the way that
the character is leaked is via uh
essentially a Boolean of um has the
scroll bar appeared or or not um and so
here's where which is detected by the
background URL on that scroll bar
exactly exactly but it here's the here's
the thing that I'm thinking can be
optimized a little bit okay we can use
animations to change values of CSS over
time so we can say like all right now
it's this font now it's this fond now
it's this font without having to do a
network request except for to load the
font of course um so I I think that
would be that would be really
interesting and I think since it's a a
you know sort of a Boolean yes or no you
kind of have to load each character
until you get a hit right so is it an a
no okay next one is it a b yes no you
know is it is it a c you know that sort
of thing right and I'm wondering if
essentially we could reduce the
complexity of doing this this search by
creating
fonts that have ligatures that
essentially do a binary search on the
possible character set so it's going to
have it's going to have a wide length if
any of the following characters uh
appear in the sequence and it's going to
have and it's going to not if the other
half and then you're halfing it each
time right so if you're dealing with
like a
256 you know standard asky character set
or whatever which I think there's less
displayable characters but whatever then
you know you need a maximum of like
seven or eight requests um to brute
force a character which is like not that
bad um okay hear me out on this hear me
out I've been I've been I've been
brainstorming okay I've been thinking
I've been thinking uh oh Joel's using
his brain careful uh I kind of need you
to help me with this dude because I was
trying to apply it apply it yesterday
and it's just kind of blowing my mind so
maybe so I was just thinking like I was
thinking about fonts as a whole because
I know there's been like very Niche
research about like using fonts in this
way as like basically kind of like um
like a blind injection where like it's
uh it's it's you have some sort of other
signal um that you're reading um as like
a canary to figure out whether or not
this is working or it's not working sure
and are you talking about the unic Cod
Point
stuff well if you define a custom font I
mean you can make those characters
larger or smaller like you can you can
change how they render and and like what
they display as so if you can get a
custom font in the page at all um and
you just change the font of everything
I'm wondering if there's some way where
you could basically have each character
be a different size so that you could
just take the width of an entire element
and then you start to subtract and you
go okay um can I subtract 26 from this
all right well there's a z in it uh can
I subtract 25 from this so there's a you
know a y in it or whatever like
something like that where you could
basically
um do some binary math or some sort of
um derivation off of the total width
based on the unique widths of each
character within the character set yeah
and then figure out what's in it without
having to also yeah see dude see this is
great I need to nerd snipe you on this
because I know that that something like
that is possible and that's what I've
been that's what I was thinking about
last night when I was sitting in bed
look staring at the ceiling like how and
essentially the problem then becomes how
do you determine remotely what the width
and height of a charact of like a
specific div is um while still doing
some semblance of word wrapping so that
you can control the number of characters
that you're applying this to which gets
really tricky in the CSS world is like
okay wrapping is highly correlated to
the width of the element and so like it
the the CSS properties just don't like
to work together in such a way that you
can isolate the characters so that you
can detect how wide the actual um thing
is and and or the actual container is
and expand it in such a way that you're
like okay there's three there's three
characters in here now there's four all
right now I can look at the you know the
width in the difference in width or the
difference in height uh like like masat
kinugawa does um in other spots in this
research um and it's it becomes a tricky
problem and and the cool thing about the
lava Dome thing is essentially what he's
able to do is check that height and
width
via JavaScript because you have
JavaScript execution right so
essentially he's using the style width
and style height um properties this is
in a different um bypass to Lava Dome
than the one we're talking about or lava
Mo lava Dome no I got you one I've got
you I've got you a potential thing here
oh my gosh you're not listening to
anything I'm saying and you're
researching stuff there's a CSS selector
called first line are you aware of this
one yes I'm aware of it I've been using
it all the time that's exactly what I'm
I'm talking about the problem is is it's
difficult to to get the right amount of
characters on the first line right and
that that first line selector is like
absolutely revolutionary you ha have to
use that um in a bunch of CSS selection
techniques but getting the correct
characters to like bump onto that first
line and then be able to tell the width
is is tricky man It's Tricky we we'll
we'll do some research together after
this episode and then maybe we can come
back and and present it but I'm I'm
running into some difficulties getting
all this stuff to work yeah I think I
think have to
check there because there are a lot of
different um CSS like measurement
selectors you know what I mean like P PX
um there's one C there's one called CH
yeah that's the character how many
characters are on the line yes yes
you're getting it Joel you're seeing
you're seeing the the craziness that is
the CSS injection world right so you can
you can set a specific amount of
characters to be on a line and then on
that then measure the length of that
line right and you should be able to
determine and the change to the width of
that line should be able to tell you the
value that was added right but it's not
that simp you can do math in CSS too
like you could multiply and stuff did
you know maybe maybe it is that simple I
don't know a cal function I've I've got
like 17 Asif 1 Asti 2 Asif 3. HTML files
with lots of different CSS in them that
I'd like to show you break word too yes
okay see Joel this is why you need to go
and read the exploits that I put into
the doc before the episode because all
of these things that you're discovering
are in the dock um yeah no triggered man
um okay so let me get back and actually
add some value to The Listener really
quick okay and instead of you and me
just doing our exploitation flow like we
always do um the thing that you need to
know
in order to do HTML attribute
exfiltration you use the sequential
import training from donut and you use
um the CSS selectors from the front and
from the back to make it super fast
right uh or you can just use Donuts tool
does that very well established battle
tested boom easy peasy to leak text
nodes is a little bit more difficult I
don't know if I'm going to get it done
in time by the uh the time that this
episode airs but I'm trying to get a
pretty cool tool in place that will
essentially be the equivalent of Donut's
um sequential import chaining tool um
but for leaking the value of text nodes
via Dynamic uh ligature Generation Um
and that sort of thing and there are
some POC codes out there uh by uh
Michael Bowski who's the guy that came
up with this original research back in
2017 um and very like very sketchy PC
code you know it's like just very you
know he just finished it and put it up
and and it's great and it gets the the
the details across but I'm trying to get
something that is you know battle tested
that it's pretty applicable you just
essentially import a CSS um stylesheet
and you specify the query selector for
the text node that you want and it just
dumps out the content of that text node
so I'm going to work on it I'm not sure
if I'm going to get there but in the
meantime if you need to actually um leak
the contents of a text node uh the
research by uh Michael Bowski
um and Linked In the description I got
you uh will be very helpful for that and
does show a basic PC of how you can
dynamically generate these ligatures
over time to leak the full value of of a
text
note you know I'm thinking we might just
have to start uh publishing some
research blog posts on uh you know on
our on our website but see here's the
thing man we just get on the on the Pod
and then we Yap about it right and and
that saves us the time of having to
write it all up because I I'll tell you
man I've been writing these
presentations for the past like
week I don't know and and the you know I
wrote the 15 page don't you love writing
isn't it great I there there are little
pieces of time with in which I enjoy
writing right like like writing the the
um the blueprint on how to go full-time
book Bounty super enjoyed that busted it
out pretty quickly you know really loved
it but actually taking the
super brainy stuff that is CSS injection
and trying to break it down and like put
it into an article that has that's easy
for people to follow is tricky and it's
I mean it's tricky to even talk about it
on the podcast so but it's really
difficult yeah I I I do agree though I
think there is definitely some Merit to
producing some sort of you know research
papers or or essentially writeups and
having it in the text Medium obviously
Brandon is doing a good job of
converting everything that we say in the
podcast into the the hacker notes and
that sort of thing but I think if we're
trying to get a little bit more in depth
on these of no I mean just unique
research more yeah yeah absolutely yeah
yeah um so anyway that that font
ligature piece the scroll bar generation
that stuff is really cool um definitely
check that out but here here is the the
thing that really sparked to this whole
thing again right which is um masat
kinugawa essentially submitted a um
issue to to Lava Dome using a new um
CSS property that I hadn't seen before
called descent
override uh which allows you to change
the height of each individual character
um in in a font pH definition right so
you're defining a custom font you define
a custom code point right you can do the
unic code code point for that specific
font um and say all right this font only
applies to like the a character whatever
and then make the a character super big
right super massive and whenever that
character gets typed into the or typed
or appears in the um the Dom then it you
know the size inflates drastically um
and so essentially he's able to do all
of this this definition without actually
using a custom font he uses I think just
comic Sands um and then this override
for the height to leak the content of um
the the lava Dome value by changing or
by detecting changes to the height like
we were talking about he has ACC to
JavaScript so he can do that if if you
don't have access to JavaScript it's
really tricky to do that but the the
Revolutionary piece about this is that
it doesn't require a font a custom font
to be imported so you can do this in a
scenario where font source is set to
something strict in the CSP um really
cool technique I love the fact that this
descent override property exists and
allows us to control the there's another
one for width as well allows us to
granular controll the width and the
height for a specific character in a
font face
definition very interesting and if you
look through actually um the font face
docs um for like the font face rule or
whatever like how it gets defined as a
custom font face um there's a ton of
different descriptors that exist and
there's a lot more that I think also
would be great candidates for this sort
of again this Canary behavior um there's
font display which determines how a font
face is displayed and whether or not it
gets downloaded and shown and it can
behave as a fallback for example so what
I'm thinking here is like you have a
default font face and then you have your
custom font face that has um characters
that are either invisible or by default
um not visible or different widths and
then it would fall back if there's no
character shown or something like that
um or or have something that renders
slowly um or something like that I don't
know I think there's definitely a lot of
really interesting candidates in here
there's
size adjust that might be the width one
you were talking about um there's font
stretch um there's descent and Ascent as
well that's the ones those are the ones
that that he uses to control the the
height and width of the yeah y size
adjust so yeah there's a lot of
different things
and you know we've talked about this so
many times we've gone through the do the
like the web or whatever HTML docs so
many times that we found like weird
consistencies or even inconsistency
things that are in the dock that do not
behave that way at all in the browser
right the of the Bas tag
um so just because it says that this is
how something works doesn't necessarily
mean that this this is how this works
but if it says that this is how it works
that's also a great starting point is
weird this is weird dude you you just
you just uh nerd sniped me with this now
I'm looking through all these different
properties there there's got to be stuff
here man this this is this is exactly
maybe there's some way we can shazz are
here too by the way like um to to fuzz
this stuff in mass or like try all the
possible options and and figure out what
the different permutations and and
possible um selectors and and
descriptors and stuff that that you can
use here yeah absolutely okay so let me
let me add one more thing to this okay
so um of course for us to leak the
contents of a text node it has to be
displaying that text right for the font
to be loaded and and for it to trigger
and for us to be able to do the whole Li
or dance or whatever right here's
something crazy that I didn't know Joel
okay you can apply display block to a
script tag and then all of a sudden the
script tag the content like the actual
content of the script tag the JavaScript
will just be displayed on the screen
like it was like a like a like a P tag
isn't that crazy it makes you wonder
what other I didn't like what happens if
you put it on a video tag or an audio
tag or a iframe or um or or um well I
think thinking uh a lot of those would
just you know display the actual you
know feature but the the crazy thing to
me about this is like I don't know I
just didn't think of style tag yeah
right I just didn't think that the
contents of a script tag I didn't think
of it as like a text node but but it is
text you know it's inside of a of a
script tag so if you just does make you
wonder a little bit about the order of
operations as well around like
it probably gets evaluated and then like
CSS gets applied later just sees it as
like an element or something but then
does that apply to like can you do that
to the Head tag or like what you know
like what where does that end right yeah
yeah and and I'm sure there's lots of
other you know weird Niche cases with
this but the reason why the script tag
is so big is is just like we were
talking about before is like there's
these there are these uh you know Blobs
of of Json the the window. state or
whatever and they're normally you know
prefixed by the same thing right window.
State equals and then big massive plop
right that is a dream come true for this
sort of text based um uh data
exfiltration piece right because
essentially when you define a prefix you
eliminate a bunch of like uh variants
like if if AB appears in like six
different spots in the whole you know uh
script blob then you could have some
problems but um you know if you have a
prefix that only if your is one then
that really helps so uh setting you know
display block to a specific script tag
and then using these font ligatures to
extract things like uh pii uh API tokens
uh curf tokens all those sort of things
um really awesome way to to exploit CSS
injection and I'm kind of salty because
I've had CSS injections and I've put so
much research into CSS injections and I
totally did not know about this
technique and you're going to hate me
because I just found more stuff but I'm
not going to I'm not going to derail you
I'm going to send it I'll send it just
send it to me man we'll we'll review it
and then maybe I can
find no don't send it to me right now
Joel what are you I'm trying to to
podcast here man um okay very
interesting so um display block can
actually display a script tag and then
you use the text node based um font
leature based uh recursive import based
leak method to actually leak your
contents of your of your text node which
will result in hopefully account
takeover or at least SE surf uh or I
guess at at minimal pii leakage in most
applications so um very cool stuff there
um I know I had one other thing that I
wanted to talk about with this uh before
we we call it your cat is very
distracting right now my cat is shees
she wants attention she does she does um
oh I did want to shout out to okay that
were kind of um helpful with this and I
will shout those out right after I
mention one other piece okay so the
tweet that I saw that you mentioned that
was just all in Japanese and was from
masatu kinugawa was essentially his
research on font ligatures and how they
are affected by um the before uh pseudo
attrib is it pseudo pseudo class
essentially the thing that allows you to
add text before a certain text blob
right or a certain text note and
essentially what he did is um there's
there's this Japanese word kabushiki
Gaya and that that's like a like for if
we were going to put it in English it's
like um limited liability company or
something right that like that right and
and it's got you know it has to be at
the end of like all of these like names
and stuff like that um and it's got a
specific ligature for it right where
they kind of put it in a square rather
than to have it all typed out and so
what he shows in this tweet is that um
you can actually use the before
attribute the before and and content uh
CSS features to trigger these font
leature sequences so let's say like
you've got a font leature that requires
four characters um and you have three of
the characters but then you put the the
first character in the CSS before um uh
before content uh you add it to the text
node with before content um that will
actually trigger the the front lature to
occur and it will be converted into a
you know that single um glyph even
though it's broken up by elements even
though it's broken up even even though
the actual text node content only
contains three of the four characters
needed you can add that character with
um the before content uh feature in CSS
um very interesting and so I thought
that was really interesting research and
it only affects some browsers um so I'm
GNA link this tweet uh in the in the
description as well um very very
interesting piece and I think this could
also be used in a scenario where you
want to add sort of like you want to
start um you want to start brute forcing
from the very beginning of a text node
and there could be overlap with other
things at other places in the in the
actual um text note itself so you kind
of got to figure out how to get it just
at the beginning and you could use this
before attribute to preen something
that's not actually in the character set
right like a squiggly line or something
like that and say okay the the font
lature is squiggly line a squiggly line
B and since squiggly line isn't going to
be anywhere else in that text node then
you know you're BR forcing right from
the beginning and it can increase some
uh reliability and consistency to the to
the uh font leature based CSS
exfiltration techniques yeah yeah
absolutely absolutely are you are you
laughing at my cat no no no I your cat
is adorable I'm laughing at myself uh
saying like font lature based CSS
injection explo like it's just so so
Mega Niche man it's just like man this
is the epitome of of uh of
nerdiness um all right man uh I think
that I mean there's just so many other
interesting pieces to talk about here
but I think that was mostly uh
everything that you need to know uh
about essentially how to exploit modern
day cist injections right you use the
research from donut on um uh sequential
import chaining plus the the CSS
selectors on attributes to leak
attribute values and then use this font
ligature based stuff to actually leak
the value of text nodes um which is
really good and if all of this doesn't
make sense uh via the audio medium uh
which I would be very surprised if it
did because this is very complex stuff
um I would encourage you to do
additional research on how exactly all
of this works uh by checking out these
two blogs okay so uh let me just let me
just format my notes a little bit here
so that uh we can know exactly what two
blogs I'm I'm talking about um the first
one is uh man why do these have to be so
named so
weird one of them is x- C3 l. github.io
and essentially this is a a post on uh
CSS injection Primitives that goes back
to 2019 and it essentially talks about
all of the different techniques you can
use um in a CSS injection talking about
recursive Imports talking about um uh
text node exfiltration via ligatures
talking about uh HTML attribute
exfiltration this blog post kind of is
similar to what I just described uh in
this in this episode regarding all of
these Primitives that you can use to do
CSS exfiltration um so that's the first
one definitely check that one out and
then the other one is this blog that I
haven't heard of before um that I've
never seen before and it's by this guy
who is a a develop who who calls himself
a developer with security interests
right and essentially if you go and look
at the blog he was a part of some
writing competition in Taiwan or
something where he had to write like a
blog post every day for 30 days and so
what he chooses is just like get to the
most like technical CSS injection xss
breakdowns CSS injection breakdowns and
it's really freaking quality stuff um so
Random so this this blog post really
made it a lot easier for me to
understand whole um font height
difference plus first line plus scroll
bar technique which masato used in one
of those things in conjunction with The
Descent override to actually leak um the
the the characters um character by
character um and he's got a really great
um description of that whole technique
so if the whole height height width
difference thing doesn't make sense to
you then I'd recommend this blog uh
Beyond xss exploring the front web Front
End security Universe um
at
aszx
github.io you're welcome for reading
that out so memorable yes just super
memorable um so yeah that's where to get
the additional research on um on CSS
injection and Joel hopefully you and I
can sit down after this episode and kind
of hash out some of these things because
I would really like to put a server out
there ideally a server that we could
actually just do it for everybody but
minimal uh a GitHub repo that
essentially allows you to just do
essentially what portswigger research
did with uh blind CSS exfiltration where
you essentially just have one URL that
you import and it just dumps everything
um for a given qu select or something
like that I think that'd be really
helpful so yeah for sure yeah so keep
keep an eye out in the uh critical
thinking Discord for me trying to drop
that and uh and I'm not sure I'll get to
it this week because I got a bunch of
stuff I gotta prep for Defcon and stuff
like that but I will get to it
eventually or else I won't sleep So
eventually all right man anything else
you want to add here at the end I think
that's it dude this is this has been a
really interesting one I got a lot of I
got a lot of followup a lot of nerd
sniping ideas yeah I got oh God I just
deleted some thing from the
dock and on that note before I delete
the entire content of this episode yeah
on the episode where we're like it will
actually be in the description too great
just delete all the notes all right man
that's the Pod right
that's the F all right peace
guys and that's a wrap on this episode
of critical thinking thanks so much for
listening and if you want more critical
thinking content head over to ctbb doow
Discord join the Discord there's lots of
great conversations and chats going on
over there and if you want to support
the show there's the Discord subscriber
tiers which give you access to master
classes amas hack alongs exclusive
scripts and an exclusive chat Channel
with us we'll see you there